Contact

8121281208 (Mobile) sampathjoseph74@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sampath-bobilli-989885121 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Channel Account Management
Operations Management
Business Alliances

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
Telugu (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

Unwavering Dedication to Service Exemplary Leadership

Sampath Bobilli

City Head @ PMI

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Summary

Experienced Strategy Alliance & Admin Business Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Business Planning, Franchise Development, Site Planning, Infrastructure Development with startups. Strong Operations professional with a Bachelor of Commerce focused in Business from St Mary's Group Of Institutions, Hyderabad.

Experience

Philip Morris International
City Head
March 2022 - Present (7 months)
Hyderabad, Telangana, India

- As a City Manager Handling entire three Promotional activities such as Shell activity, Night activity & GT-Day activity with a team of 80 candidates which includes 15 supervisors and 65 Fwps in Hyderabad.
- As a City head Here working with various Departments such as Team handling, escalations, Trainer, quality analysis, these multitasking made me much strong and experienced.
- Sourcing candidates & Recruiting and helping other cities as well to over come the shortage of manpower to strengthen the teams and to build efficient team management.
- Taking care of entire city from end-to-end daily activity through Online and Offline by observing daily instant productivity and market status.
- Preparing PPT's on market Analysis and presenting to clients on monthly basis.
- Preparing weekly review sheets for Fwps and supervisors on performance basis with appropriate reasoning's.
- Handling complete south cities such as Hyderabad, Vizag, Chennai & Bangalore with a strength of 1 city manager along with 50 candidates for each city.

- Attendance, Stock maintenance from ware house, Backend portfolio,
 Client review meetings, Daily field visits, and monthly Audit need to be done,
 Functional expertise of Salesforce Marketing Cloud
- Good understanding of end to end campaign management process
- Conduct market Research with Sales team to evaluate and finalize the outlets
- Ensure installations and its maintenance and upkeep at vendor outlets as well as acknowledgement and clearance of the bills as per PO
- Finalize beat as per switch Promotion Plan for outlet mapping and ensure deployment of promotional elements and gifts at outlets as per Activity calendar
- Responsible for the choice of outlets for implementation along with the team
- Provide feedback to the regional marketing team and sale team for improvement based on the competitor analysis and performance Responsible for training and development.

Vogo Automotive Pvt. Ltd.
Strategic Alliances Manager
February 2018 - February 2022 (4 years 1 month)
Hyderabad Area, India

- *Daily operations management of all Enterprise
- *Senior level oversight for strategic vendor and partner relationship management and input to sourcing strategies.
- *Builds successful stakeholder relationships with other leaders by developing a clear understanding of business needs and ensuring cost-effective delivery of services to meet those needs & Managing documentation.
- *Discussing with Landlords and Real-estate agents to onboard the company business, As well as searching for new landlords and agents
- *Assist in sourcing deal flow
- *Identify key partners, negotiate contracts and manage relationships on an ongoing basis to develop strong partner ecosystems in target areas.
- *Evaluate the economic and strategic costs and benefits of partnerships and work with product leadership and across functional areas to execute on the relationships
- *Drive market analysis and analyse data to determine market development strategies.
- *Identify areas for potential inorganic business development and Attend monthly meetings with the Corporate Account Managers to update information and discuss any issues

Tata Communications

4 years 4 months

Area Sales Manager

September 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 4 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

- *Postpaid growth in the given market at 6 assigned stores.
- *Improved & adequate infrastructure.
- *Improvement in NPS.
- *Expansion of Store as per the location strategy & New stores productivity as per the guidelines
- *Ensure all new franchisees' partners are aligned & imbibe serve to sell as a way of life.
- *Drive Postpaid growth & profitability.
- *Significant QOQ improvement in postpaid sales numbers as per the expected growth, Drive all LOBs through franchise Stores.
- *Drive the relevant focus products at all times.
- *Monitor performance at store level and put into action plans of improvement.
- *Local area catchment programs in conjunction with the Circle marketing team.
- *Maximize the efficiency of Circle support processes to ensure error-free retail operations.
- *Ensuring total compliance with all defined processes & systems of people Development / Team Management.
- *100% trained & certified team of FRMs & Store staff.

Senior Business Developer

November 2014 - August 2016 (1 year 10 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Business Developer

September 2013 - November 2014 (1 year 3 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Education

St. Mary's College

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Business/Commerce, General · (July 2009 - July 2013)